max2shop.com 2011-11-23

# Privacy Policy - max2shop.com

Customer Service

  * Why Buy from Us?
  * FAQ
  * Contact Us
  * Disclaimer
  * Privacy Policy
  * Shipping Information
  * Returns & Exchange
  * Warranty
  * Payment Methods
  * Order Confirmation
  * Order Tracking

| 

Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction 

Our customer information is intended to help us conduct our business in a professional manner and will not be disclosed to others. We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit max2shop.com on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. 

### 2.What Personal Information About Customers Does max2shop.com Gather? 

#### 2.1

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at max2shop.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

#### 2.2

Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other ways. Those include your personal details you enter when creating a customer account as well as product pages you are visiting and E-Mail subscriptions you are making. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store, and communicating with you. 

#### 2.3

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses max2shop.com, such as your IP address, your web browser type, operating system, URL clickstreams and similar. We use cookies for a number of purposes, for instance, to enable us to simplify the logging on process for registered users, to help ensure the security and authenticity of registered users, to provide the mechanisms for online shopping and to enable traffic monitoring, 

### 3\. Minors 

Our services are not available to Minors. If you are under 18, please do not submit any personal information to us and you may use max2shop.com only with the supervision of your parent or guardian

### 4\. Amendment 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time so that it accurately reflects the regulatory environment and our own data collection and disclosures practices. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 3 days after they are posted on this Web site. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

### We want to hear from you

Your opinion truly counts. Our Site was designed to serve the needs of our Members. Please contact us with any questions or comments. You may do this by sending an email to the [sales@max2shop.com](mailto:sales@max2shop.com)  
  
---|---
